Local 1199 Drug and Hospital Union News files 5933
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Local 1199 Drug and Hospital Union News files
1897-1988
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Local 1199 Drug and Hospital Union
5933
1 cubic feet
1 linear ft.
Records (documents).
6694386
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, January 25, 2013
EAD encoding:
Kheel Staff, April 18, 2019
Scope and Contents
Material was originally interfiled with photos in 5933 P.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 5933 P: Local 1199 Photograph Files
National Union of Hospital and Nursing Home Employees.; Bread and Roses Cultural Project; National Union of Hospital and Nursing Home Employees. Local 1199 Drug and Hospital Union (New York, N.Y.)
6694386
- 1199 Plaza (Box 1, Folder 1)
- AIDS, 1986-1988 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Calendar, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Calendar, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Calendar Duplicates, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Calendar, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Charleston Strike, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  Scope and Contents
  March-July
- Contract Campaign, News Clippings (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Drug History (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Early Ads and Printed Matter "Working In Hospitals: Then and Now" (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Early Drug Union (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Early Hospital Late 1800s - early 1900s (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Early Publications. "A Please For Shorter Hours For Druggists", 1897 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Early Publications, "Drug Clerks Voices" vol. 1 No. 2, 1918 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Early Publications, "Drug Clerks Voices" v. 1 no. 1, 1918 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Early Union Activity Pharmacists (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Miscellaneous (Box 1, Folder 17)
- El Salvadore, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  3/27
- Ferraro - Mondale Democratic Convention, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  August
- Gallery 1199, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Haym Solomon, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- Historical Job Listings (Box 1, Folder 22)
  Papers - Not Photos
- Historical Job Listings (Papers - not photos) (Box 1, Folder 23)
- Historical News Clips, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 24)
- Hospital Strikes: Fred Leon Davis (Box 1, Folder 25)
- Hospital Workers Rally For Freedom: Broadside (Box 1, Folder 26)
- Israel Support (Box 1, Folder 27)
- Johnson, Edrena, Arthur Diary (Box 1, Folder 28)
- King Jr., Martin Luther. Prayer Pilgrimage. Advertisement Speech, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 29)
- King Jr., Martin Luther. Correspondence and Speeches, 1965-1967 (Box 1, Folder 30)
- King Jr., Martin Luther "Salute to Freedom" Speech. Transcript., 1968 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  March
- Martin Luther Kings: Magazines, Clippings, Photos., 1968 (Box 1, Folder 32)
- Lawson Bartholomew, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 33)
- League Strike, New York, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 34)
- Pharmacists Union of Greater New York (Box 1, Folder 35)
- Stolzenberg, Harry. Membership Cards, 1935-1973 (Box 1, Folder 36)
- "Salute to Freedom", 1969 (Box 1, Folder 37)
- "Salute to Freedom", 1973 (Box 1, Folder 38)
- "Salute to Freedom", 1981 (Box 1, Folder 39)
- Thomas, Norman Died 19 December 1968 (Box 1, Folder 40)